Finding Aid for Leroy Barnett Photograph Collection, 1928-1965
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Leroy Barnett Photograph Collection 1928-1965
Barnett, Leroy, collector.
14 linear feet
89547 Aa 2
Archivist and historian; collection of photo prints and photo negatives, made by various state agencies, and relating primarily to rural landscapes, road construction projects, and the construction of state buildings.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection (donor no. 7596 ) was the gift of Leroy Barnett, 1988-1990.
No further additions to the collections are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Leroy Barnett is a researcher and historian of Michigan related topics.
The Leroy Barnett collection consists of ten series of photographs: Michigan State Agriculture Department, Michigan State Highway Department, John C. Mackie, Lloyd Clair Hulbert, Construction Projects (1947-1965), Postcards, Michigan National Guard, Michigan Department of Conservation, Libraries, and Events and Monuments.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Agriculture--Michigan.; Streets--Michigan--Alma.; Asparagus.; Bridges.; Cherries.; Construction industry.; Streets--Michigan--Detroit.; Drive-in theaters.; Educational buildings--Michigan.; Fairs--Michigan.; Ferries.; Food vendors.; Edsel Ford Expressway (Detroit, Mich.); Government buildings--Michigan.; Streets--Michigan--Holland.; Hospitals--Michigan.; Hotels and taverns.; Streets--Michigan--Howell.; Laboratories.; Mackie, John C.; Mackinaw City (Mich.); Mental institutions--Michigan.; Michigan. State Dept. of Agriculture.; Michigan State Fair.; Michigan. State Highway Dept.; Streets--Michigan--Paw Paw.; Police stations--Michigan.; Prison facilities--Michigan.; Progress photographs.; Remodeling.; Restaurants.; Road construction.; Roads--Michigan.; Streets--Michigan--Rochester.; Sleeping Bear Dunes (Mich.); State Line Dance.; Theaters--Michigan.; Universities and colleges--Michigan.; Woodward Avenue (Detroit, Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Michigan State Agriculture Department 1928-1948
  The photographs of the Michigan State Agriculture Department cover the period 1928 to 1948. Only three activities of the department are recorded here: the 1928 Upper Peninsula State Fair in Escanaba, Agriculture Department indoor and field laboratories, and cherry canning and factory work in Traverse City.
  - Asparagus (Box 1)
  - Cherry processing (Box 1)
  - Field laboratory vehicles (Box 1)
  - Kraft Foods cheese manufacturing plant, Pinconning, Mich. (Box 1)
  - Laboratories (Box 1)
  - Upper Peninsula State Fair, Escanaba 1928 (Box 1)
- Michigan State Highway Department 1911-1965
  The Michigan State Highway Department photographs document the activities of that department from the 1911 through the 1965. The series of photographs depicts rural road construction sites, road crews and equipment, and roads and highways. Arrangement is alphabetical by Michigan county. Large numbers of photos are available for Ingham, Kent, Livingston and Wayne Counties. Of particular interest are the photographs of drawings and models of proposed construction, which may be found in the Chippewa, Kent, Livingston, and Wayne county folders and in a folder especially for those signed by Al Roth. An interesting feature of the Wayne County photographs is the documentation of the construction of the Edsel Ford and John C. Lodge Expressways in Detroit.
  - Al Roth drawings (Box 1)
  - Alcona (Box 1)
  - Alger (Box 1)
  - Allegan (Box 1)
  - Alpena (Box 1)
  - Antrim (Box 1)
  - Arenac (Box 1)
  - Baraga (Box 1)
  - Bay (roadside stands) (Box 1)
  - Benzie (Box 1)
  - Berrien (Paw Paw, Mich.; State Line Dance Tavern) (Box 1)
  - Branch (roadside tourist park/rest stop) (Box 1)
  - Calhoun (Box 1)
  - Cass (Box 1)
  - Charlevoix (Box 1)
  - Cheboygan (ferry lines; Mackinaw City) (Box 1)
  - Chippewa (Box 1)
  - Clare (Box 1)
  - Clinton (Box 1)
  - Delta (Box 1)
  - Dickinson (Box 1)
  - Eaton (school bus) (Box 1)
  - Emmett (Box 1)
  - Genesee (Box 1)
  - Gogebic (Box 1)
  - Grand Traverse (Box 1)
  - Gratiot (Alma, Mich.) (Box 1)
  - Hillsdale (factory, drive-in, truck stop) (Box 1)
  - Houghton (harbor at Houghton) (Box 1)
  - Huron (Box 1)
  - Ingham (bridges) (Box 1)
  - Ionia (roadside stand, school bus) (Box 1)
  - Iosco (Box 1)
  - Iron (Box 1)
  - Isabella (Box 1)
  - Jackson (Box 1)
  - Kalamazoo (Box 1)
  - Kent (roadside stand) (Box 1)
  - Keweenaw (Box 1)
  - Lake (Box 1)
  - Lapeer (Box 1)
  - Lenawee (roadside restaurant, grocery store) (Box 1)
  - Livingston (Howell, Mich.) (Box 1)
  - Luce (Box 1)
  - Mackinaw (Labor Day traffic at St. Ignace) 1941 (Box 1)
  - Macomb (Box 1)
  - Manistee (Box 1)
  - Marquette (Box 1)
  - Mason (Box 1)
  - Mecosta (Box 1)
  - Menominee (Box 1)
  - Midland (Box 1)
  - Missaukee (Box 1)
  - Monroe (Box 1)
  - Montcalm (Box 1)
  - Montmorency (Box 1)
  - Muskegon (roadside tourist park/rest stop) (Box 1)
  - Newago (Box 1)
  - Oakland (Rochester, Mich.) (Box 1)
  - Oceana (Box 1)
  - Ogemaw (Box 1)
  - Ontonagon (Box 1)
  - Osceola (Box 1)
  - Oscoda (Box 1)
  - Ottawa (Holland, Mich.) (Box 1)
  - Presque Isle (Box 1)
  - Roscommon (Box 1)
  - Saginaw (Box 1)
  - Saint Clair (Box 1)
  - Saint Joseph (Box 1)
  - Sanilac (snow removal) (Box 1)
  - Schoolcraft (Box 1)
  - Shiawassee (Box 1)
  - Tuscola (Box 1)
  - Van Buren (Box 1)
  - Washtenaw (Box 1)
  - Wayne (Woodward Avenue; Ford Expressway), 2 envelopes (Box 1)
  - Wexford (Box 1)
- Michigan State Highway Department, John C. Mackie 1957-1960
  The third series concerns John C. Mackie, State highway Commissioner from 1957 to 1964. The photographs in this series illustrate his activities as Commissioner from 1957-1960. Mackie presided over many projects designed to strengthen Michigan's highway and interstate systems. The pictures are mainly of Mackie and other individuals at highway opening ceremonies or other department functions.
  - Ceremonies and meetings (Box 1)
- Lloyd Clair Hulbert, photographer 1927-1939
  The Lloyd Clair Hulbert photographs were taken by Hulbert from 1927 to 1938. The series is arranged alphabetically by Michigan county. The photos are exclusively of rural areas. Large numbers of photos exist for Alpena, Ingham, Lapeer, Tuscola, and Washtenaw counties. The Washtenaw County pictures are of the Huron River Valley and the Saline area. Generally southeastern Michigan is undocumented here: no photographs are available for Wayne, Oakland, Monroe, or Lenawee counties. Some photographs have accompanying negatives.
  - Alcona (Box 1)
  - Alger (Box 1)
  - Alpena (Box 1)
  - Antrim (Box 1)
  - Arenac (Box 1)
  - Barry (Box 1)
  - Benzie (Box 1)
  - Berrien (Box 1)
  - Calhoun (Box 1)
  - Charlevoix (Box 1)
  - Cheboygan (Box 1)
  - Clinton (Box 1)
  - Crawford (Box 1)
  - Dickinson (Box 1)
  - Eaton (Box 1)
  - Emmett (Box 1)
  - Houghton (Box 1)
  - Huron (Box 1)
  - Ingham (Box 1)
  - Ionia (Box 1)
  - Kalamazoo (Box 1)
  - Keweenaw (Box 1)
  - Lapeer (Box 1)
  - Leelanau (Box 1)
  - Livingston (Box 1)
  - Mackinaw (Box 1)
  - Macomb (Box 1)
  - Mason (Box 1)
  - Muskegon (Box 1)
  - Oceana (Box 1)
  - Ontonagon (Box 1)
  - Oscoda (Box 1)
  - Otsego (Box 1)
  - Ottawa (Box 1)
  - Presque Isle (Box 1)
  - Saginaw (Box 1)
  - Saint Clair (Box 1)
  - Sanilac (Box 1)
  - Schoolcraft (Box 1)
  - Shiawassee (Box 1)
  - Tuscola (Box 1)
  - Washtenaw (Box 1)
- Construction photographs
  With the exception of the Michigan State Fair photographs the state sponsored Construction Projects series consists of construction photos of various state-owned buildings. The Michigan State Fair photographs include a few construction pictures, but also many shots of completed but empty fair buildings and of the Fair in session during 1947.
  The Construction series is in the form of spiral bound booklets of photographs. It is arranged by type of institution then alphabetically by the name of the institution. Within each institution arrangement is alphabetically by name of building. The photographs in this series document construction projects undertaken by the State between 1947 and 1965. Both original construction and alterations to existing structures are included. The collection is especially strong in mental health facility construction projects. Dates have been noted on the contents list when they are known. If no date is listed, the date of the photographs in that book are not known. Many of the photographs also document men working on the various construction projects. These have been noted only when they are especially numerous or interesting for some reason.
  - Correctional institutions
    - Medium Security Correctional Institution and Branch Prison--Ionia
      - First building 1956-1958 (Box 2)
      - Housing unit 1960-1963 (Box 2)
      - Recreation building 1963 (Box 2)
      - Utilities 1960 (pre-construction site shots) (Box 2)
      - Vocational-academic building 1960-1961 (Box 2)
    - Michigan Reformatory--Ionia
      - Administration building 1957-1958 (Box 2)
      - Outside dormitory 1954-1955 (Box 2)
      - Powerhouse 1946-1949 (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous projects 1947-1948 (Box 3)
        (building deterioration, truck entrance, parking, boiler house, powerhouse, furnace)
    - State House of Correction and Branch Prison--Marquette
      - Cell block "B" 1956 (Box 3)
      - Cell block "G" 1965 (Box 3)
      - Chapel 1963 (Box 3)
      - Dormitory 1963 (Box 3)
      - Heating plant 1961-1962 (Box 3)
        (some photographs show men at work and construction equipment)
      - Water tank 1963-1964 (Box 3)
    - State Prison of Southern Michigan--Jackson
      - Barn (shows cows eating) (Box 3)
      - Cell blocks 4 & 5 (Box 3)
      - Chapel 1958 (Box 3)
      - Forestry building (Box 3)
        (not construction photographs)
      - Water tank (Box 3)
  - Department of Health
    - Blood fractionation laboratory 1958 (Box 3)
    - Boiler house 1948 (Box 3)
    - Vital statistics building 1956-1957 (Box 3)
  - Mental health facilities
    - Caro State Hospital
      - Adult patients building 1949 (Box 3)
      - Infirmary 1964 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous projects (Box 3)
        (landfill, sidewalks and parking, drainage, plumbing fixtures)
    - Coldwater State Home and Training School
      - Custodial buildings 1956 (Box 3)
      - Farm 1947-1949 (Box 3)
      - Hospital 1953-1956 (Box 3)
      - Laundry 1956 (site excavation) (Box 3)
      - Vocational training unit 1955-1956 (Box 3)
    - Hawthorn Center
      - Administration building 1954-1956 (Box 4)
      - Cottages 1955-1956 (Box 4)
      - Day hospital 1964-1965 (Box 4)
        (some of these pictures show men working)
    - Ionia State Hospital
      - Men's building 1962-1963 (Box 4)
      - Passages between buildings 1948 (Box 4)
        (shows existing passages and sites for proposed passages)
    - Kalamazoo State Hospital
      - Additions and repairs 1946-1948 (Box 4)
        (stairs, furnace, sewage disposal tank, water tower)
      - Central kitchen 1956 (Box 4)
      - Female center 1961-1962 (Box 4)
      - Hall "A" 1948 (porch) (Box 4)
      - Maintenance building 1957-1958 (Box 4)
      - Power plant 1958-1959, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
      - Rich colony 1953-1954 (Box 4)
    - Lafayette Clinic--Detroit 1954 (Box 4)
      (see also includes Neuropsychiatric Institute photographs)
    - Lapeer State Home and Training School
      - Boilers 1961 (Box 4)
      - Nursery (children's) 1961-1962 (Box 4)
      - School building and vocational education shops 1955-1957 (Box 4)
      - Misc. projects 1947-1949 (Box 4)
        (doctors' residences, dairy, residence service tunnel, fire escapes, lumber storage building, gas lines, etc.)
    - Michigan Rehabilitation Institute--Dormitories and commons building 1963-1964 (Box 4)
    - Mount Pleasant State Home and Training School
      - Custodial buildings 1954-1957 (Box 5)
      - Laundry 1949-1957 (Box 5)
        (also some misc. projects: power house, occupational therapy rooms, landfill, calf barn, coal storage)
      - Nursery (children's) 1958-1959 (Box 5)
      - Power plant 1955-1957 (Box 5)
        (see also laundry)
      - Service building 1956-1957 (Box 5)
        (many of these photos have a detailed description on the back; some interesting photos of a man working are included.)
      - Utility service 1954-1957 (shows men working) (Box 5)
      - Misc. projects 1946-1948 (Box 5)
        (kitchen, laundry, steam tunnel, chimney; see also laundry)
    - Neuropsychiatric Institute--Detroit 1953-1954 (Box 5)
      (see also Lafayette Clinic)
    - Newberry State Hospital
      - Chimney and water tank 1959 (Box 5)
        (loose photographs with description on the back and a memorandum from Thomas J. Bannon to Ralph Seeley)
      - Cottage "D" 1964 (Box 5)
      - Dairy barn 1948-1948 (shows cows) (Box 5)
      - Detention buildings 1956 (Box 5)
      - Doctor's residence 1949 (showing completed building) (Box 5)
      - Laundry 1964-1965 (Box 5)
      - Turbo-generator 1958 (Box 5)
      - Misc. projects 1947-1948 (Box 5)
        (street lights, road, painting projects, root storage building, doctor's residence, laundry, firestairs)
    - Northville State Hospital
      - First coal delivery September 7, 1950 (Box 5)
      - Industrial Therapy "C" 1954-1955 (Box 5)
      - Industrial Therapy "D" 1954-1955 (Box 5)
      - Occupational-recreational therapy building 1956 (Box 5)
      - Site work 1949-1952 (Box 5)
      - Utility service extension 1953 (Box 5)
    - Plymouth State Home and Training School
      - Custodial building #1 1960-1961 (shows men at work) (Box 6)
      - Custodial building #2 1962-1963 (showing men working) (Box 6)
      - Heating plant 1958-1959 (Box 6)
      - Hospital administration building 1958-1959 (Box 6)
      - Infirmary 1961-1962 (Box 6)
      - Service building 1962-1963 (Box 6)
      - Utilities services 1958-1961 (Box 6)
    - Pontiac State Hospital
      - Administration building 1953 (Box 6)
      - Boilers 1948 (Box 6)
      - Laundry building 1955 (shows men working) (Box 6)
      - Men's geriatric building 1948-1949 (Box 6)
        (includes 2 loose photos)
      - Misc. firestairs 1948 (Box 6)
      - Superintendent's residence 1953 (completed building) (Box 6)
      - Staff building 1951-1952 (Box 6)
      - Women's geriatric building 1946-1950 (Box 6)
    - Traverse City State Hospital
      - Administration building 1962-1963 (showing men at work) (Box 7)
      - Cold storage plant 1951-1952 (Box 7)
      - Fire damage and repair 1948 (Box 7)
      - Power plant 1948-1951 (Box 7)
      - Receiving hospital 1956 (Box 7)
      - Misc. projects 1947-1951 (Box 7)
        (parking, stairs, stairwells, elevator, porches, storm sewer & meter house, etc.)
    - Ypsilanti State Hospital
      - Children's unit 1963-1964 (Box 7)
      - Women patients building #B-5 1946-1948 (Box 7)
        (some photos show men working; also one photo of the Men patients' building #B-6)
  - Sanatoriums
    - Michigan State Sanatorium--Howell
      - Electrical distribution system 1949 (Box 7)
      - Employees' dormitory "B" 1950 (Box 7)
      - Heating plant 1949-1950 (Box 7)
      - Hospital building (heating tunnel) (Box 7)
      - Pasteurizing building 1946 (Box 7)
      - Sewage treatment plant 1949 (Box 7)
      - Misc. projects 1947-1949 (Box 7)
        (roads and curbing, administration building roof, weatherproofing)
    - Southwestern Michigan Tuberculosis Sanatorium--Hospital 1952-1955 (Box 7)
  - Schools for the blind and deaf
    - Michigan School for the Blind
      - Braille library and model museum 1964-1965 (Box 8)
      - Cottages 1961-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
      - Health center 1956-1957 (Box 8)
      - Physical development and sensory training building 1962 (Box 8)
    - Michigan School for the Deaf--School building 1957-1958, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
  - Michigan State Fair
    - Agricultural building 1947 (Box 8)
    - Beef cattle barn (Box 8)
    - Boundary fence 1948 (Box 8)
    - Chevrolet building 1948 (Box 8)
    - Comfort stations 1948 (Box 8)
    - Docks (Box 8)
    - Electrical wiring (Box 8)
    - Horse barn (Box 8)
    - Judging arena (Box 8)
    - Oil shed (Box 8)
    - Pasteurizing building 1948-1949 (Box 8)
    - Poultry exhibit (Box 8)
    - Quonset exhibit buildings 1948 (construction photos) (Box 8)
    - Women's building 1947 (taken while the fair was in progress) (Box 8)
    - Misc. buildings (completed, empty buildings) (Box 8)
    - Misc. exhibits and displays 1947 (taken while the fair was in progress) (Box 8)
      (includes 4 loose photographs)
  - State government
    - Dome of the Capitol 1947 (Box 8)
    - Lewis Cass building (Box 8)
    - Stephens T. Mason building (Box 8)
      (later pictures show building in use by clerical staff)
    - Parking 1948-1949 (Box 9)
      (various sites around Lansing including 2 shots of the Sears department store lot)
    - Records center 1946, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Misc. buildings 1951-1953 (Allegan St. office building, Walnut St. office building, Stephens T. Mason building) (Box 9)
  - State police
    (most of these are pictures of completed buildings)
    - Bridgeport post 1956-1957 (Box 9)
    - Clinton post 1957-1959 (Box 9)
    - Detroit--storage garage 1957-1958 (Box 9)
    - Dispatch office--East Lansing 1954 (Box 9)
    - District #4 post (Box 9)
    - District #8 post (Box 9)
    - Firing range, unidentified (Box 9)
    - Iron Mountain post (Box 9)
    - Ithaca post (Box 9)
    - Mount Pleasant post (Box 9)
    - New Buffalo post (Box 9)
  - Training schools
    - Boys' Training School--Whitmore Lake (W.J. Maxey Boys' Training School)
      - Academic unit 1963-1964 (Box 9)
      - Boiler plant 1964 (Box 9)
      - Cafeteria 1948-1949 (Box 9)
      - Cottage unit "A" 1964 (Box 9)
        (includes some photographs of the Academic unit)
      - Housing unit "B" 1964-1965 (Box 9)
      - Laundry-heating unit 1958-1960 (Box 10)
        (including some shots of the Security unit)
      - Reception center 1961-1962 (Box 10)
      - Security unit 1958-1959 (Box 10)
      - Service building 1963-1964 (Box 10)
      - Sewage treatment plant 1963-1964 (Box 10)
      - Site 1955 (original site shots and a topographical map) (Box 10)
    - Girls' Training School--Adrian--Residential unit 1957 (Box 10)
  - Universities and colleges
    - Central Michigan University
      - Arts and crafts building 1948 (Box 10)
      - Commons building 1948 (Box 10)
        (also includes Women's dormitory)
      - Education classroom building 1957-1958 (Box 10)
      - Heating facilities 1961 (Box 10)
      - Physical training building 1949-1951 (Box 10)
      - Powerhouse 1950 (Box 10)
      - Science building 1963-1964 (Box 10)
    - Eastern Michigan University
      - Fine and industrial arts building 1964-1965 (Box 11)
      - Physical education building 1963-1964 (Box 11)
      - Science building 1956-1957 (Box 11)
      - Misc. projects 1947 (Box 11)
        (dormitories, Stark-Weather Hall roof, Pease Auditorium entrances)
    - Ferris State College
      - Classroom-auditorium-office building 1960-1961 (Box 11)
      - Heating, maintenance and garage building 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 11)
      - Pharmacy and science building 1955-1957 (showing men at work on the building) (Box 11)
      - Physical education building 1963-1964 (Box 11)
      - Trades and industries building 1956-1957 (showing men at work) (Box 12)
      - Trade-technical building 1955-1956 (show men working) (Box 12)
      - Utilities 1963 (Box 12)
    - Grand Valley State College--Loutit science building 1964-1965 (Box 12)
    - Michigan Technological University
      - Civil engineering and geology building 1956-1957 (Box 12)
      - Classroom building. 1964-1965 (Box 12)
      - Mathematics and physics building 1962-1964 (Box 12)
    - Northern Michigan University
      - Administration building 1949 (Box 12)
      - Heating plant and utilities 1950-1951, 1956-1957 (Box 12)
      - Physical education building 1956-1958 (Box 12)
      - Practical and fine arts building 1962-1963 (Box 12)
      - Misc. projects 1947-1949 (Box 12)
        (temporary buildings, students' housing, powerhouse, ash handling equipment, coal conveyer hoppers)
    - Western Michigan University--Education and general classroom building 1963-1964 (Box 13)
  - Veteran's affairs
    - Michigan Veterans' Facility--Grand Rapids
      - Domiciliary building #2 1946-1948 (Box 13)
      - Power plant 1954 (Box 13)
    - Veterans' Readjustment Center--Ann Arbor--Building #1 1945-1947 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Michigan Department of Aeronautics--Capitol city airport terminal building 1957-1958 (Box 13)
    - Michigan Department of Agriculture--Departmental control laboratory 1957-1958 (Box 13)
    - Michigan Employment Security Commission--Boulevard building 1960-1961 (Box 13)
    - Michigan Liquor Control Commission--Administration and distribution building 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Monroe Scale House 1948 (Box 13)
    - Michilimackinac State Park--Toilet building 1949 (Box 13)
- Postcards
  The Postcard series consists of postcards appearing to be from the 1930s and 1940s, although undated. The postcards are mostly pictures of Michigan resort areas and include some photographs of hotels or inns, some of individual family cabins, and some of downtown areas. They are arranged alphabetically by name of town except for a few folders which include postcards not identified by town. These are: Benzie State Park, Glen Lake, Lake County, and Wolf Lake State Fish Hatchery. They are interfiled alphabetically with the rest of the series. Very few include people and these have been noted in the box list. A personal name index to the family cabins is appended to this finding aid.
  - Agate (Box 14)
    (include Agate Falls)
  - Baldwin (Box 14)
    (include Main Street; School house; State Fish Hatchery; Canterbury Park; Forest ranger station; Shrine of the Pines; Lake County Court House; Catholic Church; The Pavilion--Big Star Lake)
  - Bangor (Box 14)
  - Bear Lake (Box 14)
    (include boys in the downtown)
  - Benzie State Park (Box 14)
  - Beulah (Box 14)
    (include people in trailer park; also Bixler, William Burns cabins)
  - Bitely (Box 14)
    (include Bitely Community Church; also Kearney cabin)
  - Breedsville (Box 14)
    (family cabins include: Baker, L. Coney, Stankus)
  - Bronson (Box 14)
    (include Douglas Manufacturing Company; United States Post Office)
  - Buchanan (Box 14)
    (include Riverside Camp Store)
  - Cedar (Box 14)
    (include Old Mill)
  - Centerville (Box 14)
    (include McKinney Brothers Naturo-Pathic Clinic, also called McKinney Brothers Sanitarium and Clinic; and Covered Bridge)
  - Clare (Box 14)
    (include City Hall)
  - Colon (Box 14)
    (include the Dam)
  - Croton (Box 14)
    (include Consumer's Power Company sub-station; Hardy Dam; Road across the Muskegon River; Main Street; Bridge across the Muskegon River; Snow banks, winter of 1935/36 Road across the lake showing people)
  - Empire (Box 14)
    (include Methodist Episcopal Church; Storm Hill; The Park; Front Street)
  - Evart (Box 14)
    (include Waterworks Park with children; Bridge across the Muskegon River)
  - Fennville (Box 14)
    (include Main Street; Michigan Canners; High school; also M.C. Hutchinson cabin)
  - Ferry (Box 14)
    (include Highway bridge)
  - Frankfort (Box 14)
    (include City Park; Harbor entrance and park; Crystal Downs)
  - Fremont (Box 14)
    (include The hospital; Gerber's Strained Foods Plant; Camp Echo)
  - Glen Arbor (Box 14)
    (include Kum-An-Dyne)
  - Glen Haven (Box 14)
  - Glen Lake (Box 14)
    (family cabins include: MacDonald, Poulin (s?))
  - Gobles (Box 14)